goskills.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy policy | GoSkills

## Please read our privacy policy, part of our terms of use.

We collect personal information about users in order to provide GoSkills software services and to interact with and respond to users and also to businesses/organizations that GoSkills is provided to on a business/organizational basis.

Examples of such personal information include information provided when you fill in forms on our website to register to use it, subscribe to our courses, answer tests and quizzes, post material, enter promotions, report problems with the site, request further services, etc. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

You are encouraged to review and update your personal information, as appropriate, at any time.

In addition, for the purpose of analyzing user trends and internet traffic (see the section about cookies and measuring website traffic below), we may collect details of your visit to our website, information about your computer, Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system and browser, etc.

We reserve the right to collect any other information at our discretion, and to notify users of news and other important information via email.

## Business/Organization access

In the case of services provided on a business/organizational basis, for example where you redeem a coupon issued to your business/organization, business/organization administrators will have access to your user profile, courses, progress, certificates and other activity, regardless of whether those courses were paid for by the business/organization. If you would prefer that your business/organization does not see information about those courses for which the business/organization has not paid, you may use multiple GoSkills accounts, with separate email addresses for different courses. 

## Data storage

We will store your personal information on servers located at approved locations under contract to GoSkills Ltd. Data will be stored indefinitely and used for the purposes described in this policy.

## Confidentiality and security

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties unless:

  * you authorize us to, or
  * we are required to by law, or
  * we are required to do so to enforce our terms of use or fulfil agreements with businesses/organizations that GoSkills is provided to on an business/organizational basis, or
  * when the GoSkills certificate authenticity verification process necessarily reveals your certificate details to someone who knows your name and certificate verification number, or
  * you participate in the referral program (your first name will be shown to the person who referred you).

We strive to keep users’ personal information as secure as possible. However, as it’s impossible for any exchange of data to be completely secure, all transmissions of data are at users’ own risk.

We have implemented Google’s reCAPTCHA v3 on our site to help protect our services from bots and spam. Our use of reCAPTCHA v3 is subject to Google’s [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Use](https://policies.google.com/terms). We do not use reCAPTCHA for any other purpose.

## Cookies and measuring website traffic

We use Google Analytics and related tools to analyze how the GoSkills website is used. Google Analytics uses what are known as ‘cookies’: text files placed on users’ computers to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. Cookie information is transmitted to Google and used to evaluate and to produce statistics about website activity.

We will not use (nor allow third parties to use) such tools to track or collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our website. We will not associate any data gathered from our site with any PII from other sources, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.

## Advertising

We use remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example viewing the information page for a course might mean you see an advertisement for the course on a search results page. Third-parties sometimes use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and the third parties’ privacy policies. Some third parties allow you to set preferences for how they advertise to you, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by using cookie settings or permanently by using a browser plugin. 

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

The EC issued a formal decision recognizing New Zealand’s legal standards as being sufficient for Article 25(2) of European Union (EU) Directive 95/46/EC: that is that New Zealand’s law provides an “adequate level of data protection”. The shorthand often used is that New Zealand has “EU adequacy” or is “an adequate third country”. While GoSkills’ compliance with New Zealand’s privacy legislation is therefore sufficient, it is expected that New Zealand’s privacy legislation will continue to be developed and align more and more closely with the GDPR. GoSkills will continue to improve its alignment with the principles of both New Zealand legislation and the GDPR. 

## Links to other sites

In the event that GoSkills provides links to other websites, we take no responsibility for their content or privacy policies. Users are encouraged to read their terms of use and privacy policies before opening any links.

## Changes to this policy

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at our discretion at any time by displaying an amended version.
